Guide to the Rice University Vice President for Enrollment search records (Ann Wright), 1998-1999 UA 293
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Vice President for Enrollment search records (Ann Wright)
1998-1999
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 293
1 Linear Feet 1 box
Records related to the search committee for the position of Vice President for Enrollment, which served from 1998-1999.
Biographical / Historical
Rice University formed a search committee for the position of Vice President for Enrollment, which served from 1998-1999.
Scope and Contents
Records of the search committee whose process resulted in the hiring of Ann Wright.
Conditions Governing Access
Restricted until 2049.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Records were transferred from the committee after 1999.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges
Document Types
notes; letters (correspondence)
- Search Committee Expenses, Vision, and Documents, 1998 - 1999; 176522
  - Enrollment Management Task Force, 1998 - 1999; 176523 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vice Provost for Enrollment Position Details, 1998 - 1999; 176524 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Vice Provost for Enrollment Search Committee, 1998; 176525 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Vice Provost for Enrollment Search Expenses, 1998 - 1999; 176526 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Vice Provost for Enrollment Candidate Applications and Interviews, 1998 - 1999; 176527
  - Candidate Progress Logs, 1998 - 1999; 176528 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Candidate Resumes and Cover letters A-M, 1998 - 1999; 176529 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Candidate Resumes and Cover letters N-Z, 1998 - 1999; 176530 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vice Provost for Admission and Records Candidate Evaluations, 1999; 176531 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Vice Provost for Admission and Records Candidate Information I, 176532 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Vice Provost for Admission and Records Candidate Information II, 1999; 176533 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Vice Provost for Enrollment Interview Guide and Candidates Selected for Interview, 1998 - 1999; 176534 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Selected Candidate Transition Documents, 1998 - 1999; 176535
  - Selected Candidate Hiring Documents, Expenses, and Correspondence, 1998 - 1999; 176536 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Selected Candidate Offer Trip Feb. 1999, 176537 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Vice Provost for Enrollment Selected Candidate Work Trip Itinerary and Meeting Materials March 1999, 176538 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Vice Provost for Enrollment Selected Candidate Work Trip Itinerary and Meeting Materials April 1999, 176539 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Selected Candidate Transition Trip May 1999, 176540 (Box 1, Folder 16)